

## Contact

Berlin, Germany



+4917661652846



in /sergio-pizarro-segovia



📉 sergio.pizarroseg@gmail.com



/SergioPizarro



sergiopdev.com/

Languages

Spanish - Mother tongue

**English - Professional** working proficiency

German - B1

# **Skills**

<div class="Skills"> <Ii>HTML</Ii> <Ii> CSS</Ii> Javascript React SASS Bootstrap Stimulus Ruby on Rails <|i> SQL</|i> <<mark>li> Heroku</mark> Cloudinary

# Sergio Pizarro

# Fullstack-developer

## **Profile**

After graduating with a bachelor's degree in Industrial Engineering from the Diego Portales University in Santiago de Chile, I moved to Berlin to improve my language skills and intercultural competencies. I just completed an intensive web-developer full-stack Bootcamp at Le Wagon. During this program, I specialized primarily in backend development and now looking forward to gaining more experience in Front End technologies with React.

# **Education**

## Le Wagon

04/2022 - 06/2022

#### Web-Developer full-stack

9-week full-time intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails.

# **Diego Portales** University

03/2013 - 03/2019

### **BSc Industrial Engineering**

Industrial Engineering is an engineering profession that is focused on the optimization of complex processes, systems, or organizations by developing, improving and implementing integrated systems of people, finances, knowledge, information and equipment.

# **Experience**

### **Edipro**

01/2019 - 06/2019

#### Internship

Creation and implementation of a tool to be used in the cloud with the function of obtaining multiplatform data with Google App Script. Analysis of the obtained data to enhance the decision-making process with statisticaldescriptive schemes.

# Vínculo **Empresarial**

06/2018 - 08/2018

#### Internship

Modeling of truck loading processes with Bizagi including the simulation of multiple solutions with Arena simulator, in order to reach the optimal method according to the company's interests.

# **Projects**

### We-Pick

#### **Ruby on Rails**

Website to take desicions when you want to decide for something to do with your friends. I worked on the routes, cloudinary, controls, models, the seed for the database, CRUD and some SQL with Active Records.

## Rent a plant app

#### Ruby on Rails

Website to rent a plants depending on the city that you are. I worked in the routes, models, controls, deploy to Heroku, cloudinary, database creation, schemas and migrations, seed for the database.